[
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "What are the two experimental WIP nodes provided by ComfyUI_SeeCoder for ComfyUI?",
        "answer": "SEECoderImageEncode and ConcatConditioning are the two experimental WIP nodes provided by ComfyUI_SeeCoder for ComfyUI."
    },
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "What is the purpose of the SEECoderImageEncode node?",
        "answer": "The SEECoderImageEncode node is used to create an embedding from an image."
    },
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "What inputs are required for the SEECoderImageEncode node?",
        "answer": "The SEECoderImageEncode node requires an image to encode and a seecoder_name."
    },
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "What is the purpose of the ConcatConditioning node?",
        "answer": "The ConcatConditioning node is used to concat different embeddings together, allowing the creation of both text and visual embeddings that can be concatenated."
    },
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "What inputs are required for the ConcatConditioning node?",
        "answer": "The ConcatConditioning node requires a set of embeddings to concat something to (conditioning_to) and an embedding to concat behind those (conditioning_from)."
    },
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "Where can the SeeCoders model be found for use with ComfyUI_SeeCoder nodes?",
        "answer": "The SeeCoders model can be found on Hugging Face at the following link: https://huggingface.co/shi-labs/prompt-free-diffusion."
    },
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "Where should the downloaded SeeCoders model be placed in the filesystem for use with ComfyUI_SeeCoder nodes?",
        "answer": "The downloaded SeeCoders model should be placed in the `models/seecoders` directory."
    },
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "What is a future enhancement planned for ComfyUI_SeeCoder?",
        "answer": "Future enhancements planned for ComfyUI_SeeCoder include support for non safetensor formats and bringing attention layers in line with those used in ComfyUI."
    },
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "Are there any specific tasks that ComfyUI_SeeCoder nodes can help with?",
        "answer": "Yes, ComfyUI_SeeCoder nodes can help with tasks such as creating embeddings from images and concatenating different embeddings to create a combined representation, which can be useful in various image and text processing applications."
    },
    {
        "subject": "ComfyUI_SeeCoder",
        "question": "What is the origin of the SeeCoders model?",
        "answer": "SeeCoders is developed by SHI-Labs and the model can be found on their GitHub page: https://github.com/SHI-Labs/Prompt-Free-Diffusion."
    }
]